<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Practices on Open Practice Library</title>
    <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Practices on Open Practice Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 16:43:54 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Start At The End</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/start-at-the-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/start-at-the-end/</guid>
      <description>What is it? Start At The End is a simple exercise to identify a set of assumptions which must be tested in order achieve a long term goal. It&amp;rsquo;s a rather simple exercise, which asks participants to describe what success looks like for their work, and use this to define the goal of the effort. We default to 12 months, but it can be longer or shorter. Then, the exercise asks participants to imagine all the ways their project can fail, and using the results to enumerate key questions or assumptions that must be examined at the start of the work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualisation of Work</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/visualisation-of-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 21:41:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/visualisation-of-work/</guid>
      <description>What is Visualisation of Work? This practice involves radiating and visually representing all aspects of work. Information that is useful to team members, stakeholders and users is physically presented on walls, windows, doors and other flat surfaces and positioned in the line of sight of those people who will get value from consuming the information.
The &amp;ldquo;Information Radiator&amp;rdquo; is an artefact that is used to physically provide information to one or more people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burndown</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/burndown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 23:33:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/burndown/</guid>
      <description>What is it? A burndown chart is a visualisation of work left to do within a specified time period. The remaining work (or backlog) is often on the vertical axis, with time along the horizontal.
Teams often use burndown charts to track progress within fixed time periods (for example, Sprint Burndown charts). They can also be used to visualise progress for longer time periods and milestones (for example, Release Burndown charts).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Sentiment</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/team-sentiment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 22:53:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/team-sentiment/</guid>
      <description>What is it? Team Sentiment practices track the mood of a team and provide a mechanism for team members to rapidly feed back, either publically or anonymously, when their mood has changed.
Why use a Team Sentiment pratice? Team sentiment practices enable problems to be identified, radiated and addressed early. They enable the team to quickly discuss where one or more team members is suddenly troubled by the direction their work is going and can also provide an information radiator to assess the overall team health and feeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prep Week</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/prep-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/prep-week/</guid>
      <description>What is it? The Prep Week is a week of internal preparation before immediately before beginning a residency. It allows the team leading the engagement to immerse themselves in the particulars of the work before it kicks off. At the end of the prep week, you should have team consensus on:
 what happened during discovery and the expectations the customer has for delivery a bullet point agenda for the design week, with facilitators assigned for each item and a rough timeline a process discovery and design technique (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retrospectives</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/retrospectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/retrospectives/</guid>
      <description>What are they? Retrospectives provide opportunities for groups to reflect, inspect and adapt their ways of working. They often take place at the end of sprints but can be scheduled at any time.
Why use Retrospectives? Retrospectives facilitate continous improvement. Rather than wait until the end of a project to run a full &amp;ldquo;lessons learned&amp;rdquo; exercise for the entire delivery, we encourage taking short time boxes during delivery for the team to course correct and find ways to improve their way of working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Contract</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/social-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/social-contract/</guid>
      <description>What is it? The Social Contract is a simple, yet highly effective manner to enable team autonomy and self accountability for engagements. It looks to codify the behaviors and expectations of the team. It also provides a mechanism for the team to radiate and share its desired behaviours with management and other stakeholders.
To effectively use this practice you should look to create the following outcomes:
 Public display of the social contract Nobody is above the contract The team agreed holds each other accountable to the contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop the World Event</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/stop-the-world-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 16:20:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/stop-the-world-event/</guid>
      <description>What is it? A &amp;ldquo;Stop the World&amp;rdquo; event is when somebody on the Team identifies that the engagement is off-course for one reason or another. The FULL Team then works together to find a compromise that is acceptable to all and continues progress towards customer success. By the end of the &amp;ldquo;Stop the World&amp;rdquo; event, the team should:
 All be in agreement with the proposed compromise Identify actions or changes and owners Maintain good Psychological Safety1 among the Team  Why use &amp;ldquo;Stop the World&amp;rdquo; events?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realtime Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/realtime-retrospective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/realtime-retrospective/</guid>
      <description>Realtime Retrospective What is it? The Realtime Retrospective technique was created by Emily Webber1 in the UK. This is a great way to capture feedback from a large number of participants in realtime over an extended period of time. By the middle/end of the Realtime Retrospective you should have:
 Feedback in a timeline like fashion that are both positive and negative things A capture of the mood and reaction of people over the course of time in a realtime manner Lots of sticky notes on a wall  Why use Realtime Retrospective?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Value Stream Mapping (VSM) and Metrics-Based Process Mapping (MBPM)</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/vsm-and-mbpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/vsm-and-mbpm/</guid>
      <description>What is it? Value Stream Mapping (VSM) and Metrics-Based Process Mapping (MBPM) are third generation lean process improvement techniques, optimized for an extended organizational transformation effort. They work in tandem, where VSM is designed to view the big, macro picture and make strategic decisions with executives, and MBPM is designed to view the detailed, micro picture and make tactical improvements with front line workers. The first generation of these techniques comes from Toyota&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;information and material flow&amp;rdquo; (as documented in Lean Thinking1 and the second generation from Learning to See2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impact Mapping</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/impact-mapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/impact-mapping/</guid>
      <description>What is it? Impact Mapping is an engaging, graphical, strategic planning technique. It was introduced by Gojko Adzic in 2012. At the end of the impact map, you should have:
 A shared understand of your effort&amp;rsquo;s goal or problem statement An inventory of human behavioral changes that must occur (or not occur) for your project to be successful. These are the impact from which the technique gets it name Optionally, an inventory of project scope that could be delivered to achieve the aforementioned impacts Some sort of prioritization of scope and/or impacts A physical or digital diagram with the above information  Why use Impact Mapping?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Agenda</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/agile-agenda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/agile-agenda/</guid>
      <description>What is it? The Agile Agenda is a simple, yet effective way to manage the agenda for an in person workshop using sticky notes and a whiteboard. The basic idea is draw a days calendar on to the whiteboard, split it into 2 or more tracks, write agenda items on sticky notes (with owners!) and then place them on the whiteboard in the correct time slot. Review your agenda in the morning, and then come back to it throughout the day, updating as need be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Storming</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/event-storming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/event-storming/</guid>
      <description>What is it? Event Storming is a rapid, interactive approach to business process discovery and design that yields high quality models. It was introduced in a blog by Alberto Brandolini1 in 2013. At the end of the event storm, you should have:
 A shared understand of the business process you are building as part of the project, including:  which steps should be considered in scope and which steps are out of scope the users involved in the process an initial inventory of UI screens for the process an initial inventory of Aggregates2  A physical diagram with the above information, which can be transferred to a digital format  Why use Event Storming?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Story Mapping</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/user-story-mapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/practices/user-story-mapping/</guid>
      <description>What is it? User Story Mapping is an evolution of the traditional Agile backlog, made popular by Jeff Patton in 20081. It&amp;rsquo;s an effective practice for creating lightweight release plans that can drive standard Agile delivery practices. At the end of user story mapping, you should have:
 A backlog of scope items (captured as stories or simply feature titles) the team believes can be delivered in the planning window.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>