<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Open Practice Library</title>
    <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Open Practice Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 09:15:17 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Way of Working</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/way-of-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 09:15:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/way-of-working/</guid>
      <description>This is the Way all of the concepts and terms come together and form our Way of Working. Don&amp;rsquo;t want to read through all of this? visit this video .
Our framework is built around a transportation metaphor, the idea that you want to be immersed in Red Hat’s culture and technology to take you from one place to another.
And thus we refer to every customer engagement as a Journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms Defined</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/terms-defined/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 11:15:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/terms-defined/</guid>
      <description>Journeys These are the paths that our customers typically take when joining us on a Red Hat Open Innovation Labs engagement. Journeys represent the entirety of the engagement; from the beginning conversations to the sad good-byes. Using a Transportation metaphor, Journeys are the experiences you get, fun you had and what you learned when traveling from a West Coast City to an East Coast City with friends.
See all Journeys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 17:03:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rht-labs.github.io/practice-library/about/</guid>
      <description>Red Hat Open Innovation Labs is creating an Open Practice Library! The library&amp;rsquo;s source is in a public GitHub repo and is licensed under Apache 2.0.
Goals of this Library While this is intended for everyone who has an interest in learning more about the Red Hat Open Innovation Labs processes and practices, this Open Practice Library has two main goals in mind.
Share the Big Picture Describe how Red Hat and Red Hat Open Innovation Labs use practices to accomplish engagement success.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>